本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
准备关门啦
Ta dum, locking up
走开  负鼠  走开
Shoo, possum, shoo.
麦戈科特你个饭桶  快走
Git, McGucket, git!
餐厅  晚安啦
Ta dum, ta dum good night, diner.
小树  晚安啦
Good night, trees.
偷我派的小矮人们  晚安啦
Good night, tiny men stealing my pie.
等等  什么
Wait. What?!
伸直你的膝盖  是膝盖
Lift with your knees. No, your knees.
如果我再有一个小时吃不到东西
If I go one more hour without eating,
我就只能采取吃人的办法了
I'm gonna resort to cannibalism.
女士
Ma'am.
魔法小矮人
Little magic men.
这意味着什么  我该怎么办
What does it mean? What do I do?
是的  你好  我想报告一些事情
Yes, hi. I'd like to report something.
我正在格里丝餐厅
I'm at Greasey's diner.
你绝对不会相信我所看到的东西
You won't believe what I've witnessed.
它太不可思议了  太莫名其妙了
It's unbelievable. It's indescribable.
它
It's...
未曾有人见过
It is unseen.
好了  回到派
Well, back to pie.
我刚刚差一点就把你吃了  史蒂夫
I was this close to eating you, Steve.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： Peace  Tracy  Enpistu
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第七集
Gravity Falls  S02E07  Society of The Blind Eye
谁是
作者？
好了  作者  你到底是谁
All right, author, who are you?
你到底是
Who are...
又一支咬坏的钢笔
Not again.
思考用笔
嗨  小老弟  你看我拿到了什么
Hey, bro-bro, look what I got.
好耶  一个脏脏的绿瓶子
Yay, a filthy green bottle.
这是来自美男鱼的瓶中信  记得他吗
It's a bottle message from Mermando, remember?
他的身体一半是鱼尾  另一半赤裸上身
He was part fish, part shirtless guy.
要是他想跟我复合了怎么办
What if he wants to get back together?
我不会助长你的希望的  梅宝
I wouldn't get your hopes up, Mabel.
太迟了  希望值已经一路飙升了
Too late. Hopes are way, way up!
“亲爱的梅宝” 到目前都还不错
"Dear Mabel..." So far so good.
“我怀着沉重的心情”
"It is with a heavy heart..."
到目前也还不错
So far, so good.
“我必须告知你  我要结婚了”
"That I must inform you, I'm getting married"?!
我就知道会这样
And there it is.
“为了避免海下的内战
"In order to prevent an undersea civil war,
包办婚姻  我与海牛公主”
arranged wedding, queen of the manatees..."
而且她还这么美丽
And she's so beautiful.
怎么会这样啊
This can't be happening.
噢  梅宝  你总会放下他的
Oh, Mabel, you'll get over him eventually.
你是不会懂的  迪普
You don't understand, Dipper.
到这里的第一天  我就为夏日浪漫恋情做了一页剪贴簿
On my first day here, I made this page for summer romances.
但你看看我的运气
Look at my luck.
到头来都是些小矮人  神经病孩
Turned out to be gnomes, child psycho,
和自己的手亲热的变态木偶家
made out with his own hands.
再加上现在
And now...
夏日浪漫恋情
我只希望能永远忘记他们
I wish I could just forget about them forever.
失败
嘿  如果这算是个安慰的话
Hey, if it's any consolation,
我的夏日任务也不怎么成功
my summer mission isn't a huge success either.
我仍然在寻找这本笔记的作者
I'm still trying to find the author of this journal.
而现在手提电脑被毁了  我失去了所有能找到他的线索
With his laptop smashed, I've lost any lead in finding him.
等一下  迪普  快看
Wait a minute. Dipper, look!
-透过瓶底看  -快点照做
- Through your bottle? - Just do it.
麦戈科特实验室
"McGucket labs."
等等  是老头儿麦戈科特
Wait. Old man McGucket?
迪普  你不会认为
Dipper, you don't think...
不可能啊
Couldn't be.
这一点都说不通  除非
Doesn't make any sense, unless...
这个贴在这里
This matches with this.
这个与这里连上
This goes over here.
然后这名字就是  那么这就意味着
And then the name... so that would mean
难道是老头儿麦戈科特写了这本笔记
old man McGucket wrote the journal?!
我是帅壕  姑娘  我们帅壕
<i>Am I blanchin', girl, we blanchin' </i>
我住在豪宅
<i>I live up in a mansion</i>
我是帅壕  姑娘  我们帅壕
am I blanchin', girl, we blanchin'
我住在豪宅
I live up in a mansion
呃  我被这破歌彻底洗脑了
Ugh! I can't get that terrible song out of my head.
你是指李大狗的《直通帅壕》
You mean "Straight Blanchin'" by Li'l Big Dawg?
这是今夏最抓耳的单曲
It's the catchiest song of the summer.
到底什么是帅壕
What is blanchin'?
说唱歌手不该瞎编词语吧
Rappers can't just make up words.
说唱歌手都很有远见  温蒂
Rappers are visionaries, Wendy.
如果他们让我吃掉自己的裤子
If they told me to eat my own pants,
我也会照做的
I would do it.
吃掉你自己的裤子  吃掉你自己的裤子
<i>Eat your own pants, eat your own pants</i>
看来我别无选择了
I guess I have no choice.
温蒂  苏斯  我们必须得去拜访老头儿麦戈科特
Wendy, Soos, we need to go see old man McGucket.
-其他的我们在路上解释  -啊
- We'll explain on the way. - Gah!
嘿  那工作怎么办
Hey, what about work?
孩子们
Kids!
苏斯为什么在吃他自己的裤子
Why is Soos eating his own pants?
重力泉垃圾场
老头儿麦戈科特  你在吗
Old man McGucket, are you here?
来啊  乡巴佬
Here, hillbilly, Billy, Billy, Billy.
花了一个小时才想出这说法  但也是值了
Took an hour to think of this, but it was worth it.
麦戈邋遢！
快滚开  你们这些恬不知耻
Get outta here, you salt lickin',
无家可归的
hornswagglin'...
麦戈邋遢  他们说得没错
Mcsuckit. They got me good.
有访客
Visitors!
快进来  快进来  小心那些生锈的金属
Come, come. Pull up some rusty metal.
你们正好碰上我每小时与住在镜子中的乡巴佬
You're just in time for my hourly turf war with the hillbilly
进行的圈地运动时间
what lives in my mirror.
不要在我洗澡的时候盯着我看
Quit starin' at me when I bathe!
别装了  麦戈科特
You can drop the act, McGucket.
我知道你就是这本笔记的作者
I know you're the author.
你研究了这座小镇的秘密并且写了这本书
You studied the mysteries of this town and wrote this book.
伙计  你就是那位迪普寻找了整个夏天的天才
Dude, you're the genius Dipper's been searching for all summer.
啊  天才
Uh, genius?
我不是天才
I'm no genius.
我一生从没做过什么有价值的事
I never done nothin' worthwhile in my life.
所有人都知道我是个没有优点的无名小卒
Everyone knows I'm no good to nobody.
我都不记得我以前是什么样子了
I can't remember what I used to be,
但我肯定是个大窝囊废  才落到现在这个地步
but I must've been a big failure to end up like this.
本地疯子继续击穿底线
但是笔记本上有你的名字
But the laptop has your name on it.
那这本书你记得吗  你确定你没有写过这个
What about this book? Are you sure you didn't write it?
来  仔细看看
Here, look closely.
我说过了  我想不起来
I told you, I don't recall.
1982年之前的一切都很模糊了
Everything before 1982 is just a blur.
都很朦胧
Just a hazy...
盲目之眼
The blind eye!
长袍  那些人  我的思想
Robes. The men. My mind.
-他们对我做了什么  -谁做的
- They did something. - Who did?
我  噢  我想不起来
I... oh, I don't recall.
噢  可怜的老头儿
Oh, you poor old man.
难怪你的精神那么
No wonder your mind's all...
你曾经遭受过巨大的折磨
You've been through something intense.
会不会是麦戈科特知道了些
What if McGucket learned something
不应该知道的秘密
he wasn't supposed to know,
然后某个人  或者某个东西  就搅乱了他的思想
and someone, or something, messed with his mind?
我们必须查个水落石出
We've got to get to the bottom of this.
好好想想  伙计  你能记得的最早的事是什么
Think, dude. What is the earliest thing you can remember?
呃  我觉得是这个吧
Uh, this is, I think.
博物馆发现
迷失老人
历史博物馆
The history museum.
我们就去那里
That's where we're going.
我是帅壕  姑娘  我们帅壕
<i>Am I blanchin', girl, we blanchin' </i>
呃  苏斯
Ugh, soos!
我会给你买张新的
I'll buy you a new one.
重力泉历史博物馆
你好  有人吗
Hello? Anyone here?
好了  用敏锐的眼光扫视一切有蹊跷的东西
All right, keep your eyes peeled for anything suspicious.
梅宝  你还好吗
Mabel, are you okay?
你刚路过一只猫咪却没有摸它
You just walked by a cat without petting it.
噢  温蒂  我看到的一切都让我想起我那些失败的恋情
Oh, Wendy, everything I look at reminds me of my failed romances.
那个防腐的心脏
That formaldehyde heart.
那个浪漫的立体模型
That romantic diorama.
甚至这里还有张我上一任暗恋对象的海报
Even this poster of my most recent ex-crush.
啊  真是够了
Aw, come on!
你最初的回忆就是在这里
So your last memory was here.
-想起些什么了吗  -各位  快看
- Anything coming back? - Guys, look!
嘿  谁在那里
Hey, who's there?
哎哟  我的天哪  他消失不见了
Well, kettle my corn. He vanish-ified.
这没道理啊
It doesn't make sense.
他去了哪里
Where did he go?
我觉得这些眼球都在盯着我看
I feel like all these eyeballs are a-watchin' me.
等等
Wait.
还真是
They are.
移到边上
Move aside.
正点
Jackpot!
一条秘密通道
A secret passageway.
我们的一定要鬼鬼祟祟的
We'll have to be stealthy.
如果遇到危险我会发出一个信号
I'll hambone a message if there's trouble.
郊狼
要
来
抢
我们的
牛杂碎
了。
我不知道这是什么意思
I have no idea what that means.
这次会议的主题是谁
Who is the subject of our meeting?
这个女人
This woman.
懒苏珊
Lazy Susan?
你都看到了什么
What is it that you have seen?
说话
Speak!
那会儿我刚离开餐馆
Uh, well, uh, I was leaving the diner,
就看见那些长着胡子的小东西
and I saw these little bearded doodads,
然后我就这样  啥
and I was, like, "whaaaa?"
好了好了
There, there.
你不会这样啥太久了
You won't be "like whaaaa" for much longer.
这是什么小发明
What is that gizmo?
看上去像个电吹风
It looks like a hair dryer.
小矮人
你们是理发师吗
Are you guys barbers?
懒苏珊  你对这些长着胡子的小人都知道些什么
Lazy Susan, what do you know of little bearded men?
我头脑空空
My mind is clear,
多亏了盲目秘社
thanks to the society of the blind eye.
未曾有人见过
It is unseen.
我的天哪
Oh, my gosh.
他们抹去了懒苏珊的记忆
They erased lazy Susan's memory.
伙计们  你们都看见了么
Guys, are you seeing this?
他们刚抹去了懒苏珊的记忆
They just wiped lazy Susan's memory.
他们应该把那难看的睫毛膏也抹掉的
They should've wiped off that awful mascara.
我觉得很漂亮啊
I think she looks beautiful.
她已经尽全力了  苏斯
She's doing the best she can, soos.
喔  刺激到敏感神经了
Whoa, touched a nerve there.
懒苏珊  你感觉如何
Lazy Susan, how do you feel?
我感觉好极了
I feel great!
我甚至不记得出什么问题了
I can't even remember what was wrong,
还有我来这儿做什么
or what I'm doing here,
我究竟是男是女
or if I'm a man or a woman.
我们会保存好你的记忆
Your memories will be safe with us,
将它埋在遗忘大厅里
buried in the hall of the forgotten.
埋在遗忘大厅里
Into the hall of the forgotten.
咒语念得很好嘛  小伙子们  你们是练习过吗
Good chanting, boys. Have you been practicing?
休会
Meeting adjourned.
-回不见  -回不见
- Unsee you later. - Unsee you later.
回不见
Unsee you later.
太神奇了
Amazing.
一个消除记忆的邪恶秘密团体
A secret society of evil mind erasers.
我敢打赌他们一定是很久以前就抹掉了你的记忆
I'll bet they erased your memory a long time ago.
如果我们能找出他们把你的记忆藏在哪儿
If we could find where your memories have been hidden,
也许就将是解开重力泉镇所有秘密的关键所在
it could be the key to unlocking all the mysteries of Gravity Falls.
好了  梅宝  温蒂  你们俩呆在这儿
All right, Mabel, Wendy, you two stay here
确保那些穿长袍的家伙不会回来
and make sure those robe guys don't come back.
耶  女生俱乐部
Whooo! Girls club.
苏斯  你和我还有麦戈科特  我们去找遗忘大厅
Soos, you, me, and McGucket are gonna go find the hall of the forgotten.
跟着那个帽子
Follow that hat!
不许动  有人吗
Halt! Is someone there?
啊  我们该怎么办  我们要去哪儿
Aah! What do we do? Where do we go?
晕  这些玩意儿的做工也太差了
Man, these are really poorly made.
我发誓我听到有人的声音
I could've sworn I heard someone.
可能又是门卫
Probably just the janitor
亲那个拓荒女人蜡像的声音吧
kissing that wax settler woman again.
诶哟  提醒我删掉那个记忆吧
Woof! Remind me to erase that from my memory.
它在那儿
Whew! There it is.
快点
Hurry!
哎呦我去  我的亲娘四舅姥爷啊
Honey fogelin', salt lickin' skullduggery.
伙计  你得教我一些你们老年人的感叹语
Man, you have got to teach me some of those old-man swear words.
我就不明白了  温蒂
I just don't get it, Wendy.
我经常和人拥抱  我能打着嗝说出字母表
I hug a lot, I can burp the alphabet,
我的衣服一摩擦就会发出香味
I have scratch and sniff clothing.
为什么男孩们还是离开我
Why does every boy leave me?
切  谁在乎啊  男生最讨厌了
Pfft, who cares? Boys are the worst.
别再为这事闹心了
You shouldn't get hung up, man.
也许是我开始的时候太强势了
Maybe I come on too strong, you know?
你的开场白是啥
Well, what's your opener?
假装我是个男生
Pretend I'm a boy.
嗯  男人味
Mmm, testosterone.
嗨  我是梅宝  我十二岁  有一头猪
Hi. I'm Mabel! I'm 12 and own a pig!
想和我结婚吗
Wanna get married?!
实话跟你说  你的表现很完美
Honestly? That was perfect.
忘掉那些男生吧  老妹
You should just forget about guys, man.
温蒂  你说的对  忘了那些男生
Wendy, that's it. Forget about guys.
我只要把“夏日恋情”写到这机器里
I just need to type "summer romances" into this thing,
然后就再也不会为它们难过了
and I won't feel bad about them anymore.
喔  等等  梅宝
Whoa, hold up, Mabel.
我们都不知道这玩意儿究竟是怎么回事呢
We don't even know what that thing does.
你很可能会不小心擦掉别的记忆
You could accidentally erase, like,
比如阅读能力啊或者呼吸或者
learning to read or breathe or...
你怎么都忘不掉的难听的暑期之歌
Or one of those terrible summer songs you can't get out of your head?
看这些管子
Look at all these tubes.
全镇的人肯定都被消除过记忆
People must've been getting their memories erased all over town.
看这个
Whoa, look at this.
罗比的记忆
好的  罗比  你都看见了什么
Yes, Robbie, what is it that you have seen?
那个厉害的功夫小子攻击了我
<i>So I was attacked by this magic kung fu guy</i>
他朝我扔火球什么的
<i>that was throwing, like, balls of fire at me.</i>
不过我打得他落花流水
<i>I kicked his butt, though.</i>
罗比  说实话
Robbie, speak honestly.
我被一个十二岁的男孩救了
<i>I was saved by a 12-year-old.</i>
他们为什么要消除人们的记忆呢
Why are they erasing people's memories?
我还是不明白
I still don't get it.
快看啊  伙计们
Looky, fellers.
别人不就是这么叫我的吗
It's those words what people call me.
老兄  你的记忆  我们找到了
Oh, dude, your memories. We did it.
我拿  我拿
Grabby grabby.
我拿到了
I got it!
夏日恋情
我说不好  梅宝  你真的觉得这是个好主意吗
I don't know, Mabel. Are you really sure this is a good idea?
所有的主意都是好主意
All ideas are good ideas.
你听见了吗
Do you hear that?
我脑子里的警报声又响了
The alarm in my brain is a-ringin' again. Ah!
不许动  是谁
Halt! Who's there?
-糟了  -快跑
- Oh, no! - Run.
这边  给我回来
This way. Get back here!
你这次真的搞砸了  费多福
Oh, you've really tarred it up now, Fiddleford.
这全都是你的错
This is all your fault.
我的胡子上怎么还贴了创可贴
Why does my beard have a bandage?
没道理啊
Does that even make sense?
为什么没人指出来
Why has no one pointed that out?
好了  我们应该是安全了
Okay, I think we're safe.
我们在玩猜猜我是谁吗
We playing "guess who"?
老兄  我知道是你  迪普
Dude, I know it's you, Dipper.
好粗壮的手啊
Such big, strong hands.
你们不该来这儿的
You shouldn't have come here.
我们不会轻易放弃我们的秘密的
We do not give up our secrets lightly.
你们这些穿着浴袍的怪胎都是什么人
Who are you bathrobe-wearing freaks?
为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你那奇怪的英式口音是怎么回事
What's with your creepy British accent?
反正我们也要消除你们的记忆了
Well, I suppose we are going to erase your minds anyway.
托比・迪特敏德
Toby Determined?
巴德・格里夫
Bud Gleeful?
那个农夫
That farmer guy?
娶了啄木鸟的那个怪人
Creepy dude who married a woodpecker?
你也在  顺便问一句  你们的婚姻还好吗
You, too? How's that marriage goin', by the way?
哦  很好很好
Oh, great, great.
一点都不好
Not great.
你以前从没见过我
And you've never met me before.
即使你见过  你也不会记得
And if you had, you wouldn't remember.
我是瞎子伊凡
I am blind Ivan,
我们就是盲眼秘社
and we are the society of the blind eye.
很多年前由我们的创始人创办的
Formed many years ago by our founder...
我们的创始人  有人记得他叫什么吗
Our founder... does anyone remember who he was?
我们自己也经常使用那个射线
We've been usin' that ray on our own brains an awful lot.
你们为什么要这么做  你们这是图什么
Why would you do all this? What do you have to gain?
你们一定也发现了
As you have no doubt discovered,
重力泉镇一直被超自然现象所困扰
<i>Gravity Falls is a town plagued with supernatural strangeness.</i>
没人知道如何阻止夜间突然袭来的怪异事件
<i>No one knew how to stop the things that went bump in the night,</i>
于是我们的创始人就发明了这个好东西
so our founder invented the next best thing--
让我们忘掉的方法
<i>a way for us to forget.</i>
我们主动去帮助受困扰的镇民
<i>We took it upon ourselves to help the troubled townsfolk</i>
通过消除记忆帮他们忘掉看到的奇怪的事情
<i>by erasing the memories of the strange things they've seen.</i>
现在重力泉镇的人们
<i>Now the people of Gravity Falls</i>
无知而快乐地生活着
<i>go about their lives ignorant and happy,</i>
多亏了我们
<i>thanks to us.</i>
作为福利
And as a perk,
我们也帮自己忘掉困扰我们的事情
we help ourselves forget things that trouble us.
每个人都有自己想忘记的事情
Everyone has something they'd rather forget.
事实上  你的亲姐姐也准备用那个射线来着
In fact, your own sister was about to use that ray on herself.
我没说错吧
Isn't that right?
梅宝  有没有搞错
Mabel? Seriously?
哈哈  貌似是这么回事
Ha-ha. Maybe.
你难道没发现吗  这会毁掉我们的生活的
Don't you see? This is ruining lives.
你看麦戈科特老头儿
What about old man McGucket?
他住在小窝棚里  只能和动物说话
He lives in a hut and talks to animals,
都是因为你
thanks to you.
你难道不为此感到内疚吗
Don't you feel bad about that?
好像有一点
Mmm, maybe a little.
现在没了
But not anymore.
可不能让你们把在这里知道的东西告诉其他人
You won't be telling anyone else what you've learned here.
夏天
和你们的夏天说再见吧
Say good-bye to your summer.
伙计们  如果我们即将忘记一切
Guys, if we're gonna forget everything,
有些心里话我一定要说出来
I got some stuff I wanna get off my chest.
梅宝  这个夏天的前半段我一直以为你的名字是“美泡”
Mabel, for half the summer, I thought your name was maple,
跟糖浆似的  没人纠正过我
like the syrup. No one corrected me.
（注：枫树英文即maple，可以做糖浆）
我的动物毛绒玩具  我只爱其中一部分
I only love some of my stuffed animals,
我内疚得快要死掉了
and the guilt is killing me!
我有时候拽词拽得自己都不知道是什么意思
Sometimes I use big words and I don't actually know what they mean.
我是说  我应该是个聪明人才对
I mean, I'm supposed to be the smart guy.
如果我不是聪明人  那我是谁
If I'm not the smart guy, who am I?
好吧  其实我的脾气根本没那么好
Okay, I'm not actually laid back.
我压力很大  差不多每时每刻吧
I'm stressed, like, 24/7.
你们见过我的家人吗
Have you met my family?
行了  别闹孩子脾气了
Oh, stop being a bunch of babies.
麦戈科特
McGucket?!
我从采矿展台抄来了武器
I raided the mining display for weapons.
像乡巴佬一样战斗吧  伙计们
Now fight like a hillbilly, fellers.
谁也别惹我
Nobody better mess.
痢疾
西部瘟疫
他们知道得太多了  别让他们跑了
They know too much. Don't let them escape!
把这首歌赶出脑袋吧
Get this song outta your head.
痢疾来找你了  老兄
Dysentery's gonna get you, dawg.
我去拿记忆管
I gotta get the memory tube.
你休想
Oh, no, you don't.
梅宝  接着
Mabel, catch.
我要了  谢谢
I'll take that, thank you.
放弃吧  小子
Give it up, boy.
你是敌不过这难以抵挡的力量
You're no match for the unstoppable power of...
没错  我在袍子里什么都没穿
That's right, I don't wear nothin' under my robe.
不打算为这事道歉
Not gonna apologize for that.
或许你们这帮大惊小怪的人才该道歉
Maybe y'all should apologize for bein' a bunch of prudes.
恶心
Eww!!
该把这个永久消除掉
Time to erase that forever.
-把那管子给我  -绝不
- Give me that tube. - Never!
那记忆是属于麦戈科特的
That memory belongs to McGucket.
秘社的秘密是属于我们的
The society's secrets belong to us.
结束了
End of the line.
到了明天  这一切都只是场噩梦罢了
By tomorrow, this will all seem like a bad dream.
对你们宝贵的记忆说再见吧
Say good-bye to your precious memories.
不
No!!
麦戈科特  你替我挡了一枪
McGucket, you took a bullet for me.
我的天  你没事吧
Oh, my gosh! Are you okay?
我一直都会没事的
Okay as I'll ever be.
什么
What?
这个为什么不管用了
Why... isn't... this... working?
使出吃奶的劲儿打我吧  秃头
Hit me with your best shot, baldy.
我的脑袋疯癫了三十多年了
My mind's been gone for 30-odd years.
你是没法再弄坏已经坏掉的东西的
You can't break what's already broken.
说晚安吧  萨利
Say good night, Sally.
放了我们
Unhand us!
被绑着不那么好玩吧
It isn't so fun being tied up, is it?
-嘿  想不想在他们脸上乱涂  -什么
- Hey, wanna draw on their faces? - What?
嘿  住手
Hey, stop that!
知识
屁股
这可不好玩
That's not funny.
相当好玩
It's pretty funny.
这真是客观存在的好玩啊
It's, like, objectively funny.
我们会报仇的
We'll have our revenge.
我们绝不会忘记你们的所作所为
We'll never forget what you've done.
我想你们应该会忘记
Oh, I think you just might.
盲目秘社
笑一个
Say cheese.
感谢今晚光临博物馆参加淘金者铭记之夜
Thanks for visiting the museum for gold miner appreciation night.
别忘了出门时给淘金者一点小费
Be sure to tip the gold miner on your way out.
不好意思  我叫什么名字
I'm sorry, but what's my name?
我在哪儿
Where am I?
那位好像有点消除过头了
Oh, might have overdone that one.
你的名字叫图图・麦邦博斯纳兹
Your name is Toot-toot McBumbersnazzle.
你是个四海为家的班卓艺人
You're a traveling banjo minstrel,
你的心中有一首歌
with a song in your heart
头顶有搞笑的纹身
and funny tattoos on your head.
没错  我是图图・麦邦博斯纳兹  好耶
Yes, I am Toot-toot McBumbersnazzle. Cheers!
图图是我的名字
Toot-toot is my name
好了  麦戈科特
All right, McGucket.
准备好观看你的记忆
Are you ready to see your memories?
弄清楚你到底是谁了吗
Find out who you really are?
我不确定
I'm not so sure.
如果我不喜欢所看到的一切怎么办
What if I don't like what I see?
咱们都走到这一步了  来吧
We've come all this way. Go on.
第1天
我是费多福・哈德隆・麦戈科特
<i>My name is Fiddleford Hadron McGucket,</i>
我希望自己没看到过之前所见的东西
<i>and I wish to unsee what I have seen.</i>
我的老天爷呀
Sweet sarsaparilla.
过去的一年
<i>For the past year,</i>
我一直在给一位来访的研究员做助手
<i>I have been working as an assistant for a visiting researcher.</i>
他将自己在重力泉的发现
<i>He has been cataloguing his findings</i>
记载在一系列日志上
<i>about Gravity Falls in a series of journals.</i>
我帮他建造了一台机器
<i>I helped him build a machine</i>
他相信这台机器能够造福全人类
<i>which he believed had the potential to benefit all mankind,</i>
但事情不太对劲
<i> but something went wrong.</i>
我决定退出这项目
<i>I decided to quit the project.</i>
第1天
但是我整夜睡不着觉
<i>But I lie awake at night,</i>
我的所作所为在脑海中挥之不去
<i>haunted by the thoughts of what I've done.</i>
我发明了一台机器
<i>I believe I have invented a machine</i>
我相信它能永久消除我头脑中的那些记忆
<i>that can permanently erase these memories from my mind.</i>
试验品一号
<i>Test subject one.</i>
费多福
<i>Fiddleford.</i>
第5天
成功了  我什么也想不起来了
<i>It worked! I can't recall a thing.</i>
我将它命名为盲目秘社
<i>I call it the society of the blind eye.</i>
第22天
我们可以通过消除糟糕的记忆
<i>We will help those who want to forget</i>
来帮助那些想要遗忘的人
<i>by erasing their bad memories.</i>
今天我遇到了一群小矮人的聚集地
<i>Today, I came across a colony of little men.</i>
第74天
非常恶心
<i>Very disturbing.</i>
我要忘记这件事
<i>I would like to forget seeing this.</i>
我今天在镇上不小心又撞了一辆车
<i>I accidentally hit another car in town today.</i>
第189天
我觉得糟搞透了  糟糕
<i>I feel Terri-bibble. Terrible.</i>
我最近总是忘掉某些词语
<i>I've been forgetting words lately.</i>
不知道是不是有什么副作用
<i>I wonder if there are any negative side effects...</i>
我看到湖里有东西  有个大家伙
<i>I saw something in the lake, something big!</i>
第273天
我的头发掉光了
<i>My hair's been a-fallin' out,</i>
第618天
所以从稻草人那儿拿了这顶帽子
<i>so I got this hat from a scarecrow.</i>
我的裤子是不是穿反了
<i>Hey, are my pants on backwards?</i>
第？？？天
麦戈科特  我很抱歉
Oh, McGucket. I'm so sorry.
没事
Aw, hush.
你们几个孩子帮我找回了记忆  就像你们说的
You kids helped me get my memories back, just like you said.
但你真的想找回那样的记忆吗
But did you want those memories back?
这么多年过去  我终于知道自己是谁了
After all these years, I finally know who I am.
或许我过去是把事情搞砸了
Maybe I messed up in the past,
但是现在我知道是怎么回事了
but now that I seen what happened,
我可以开始着手重整旗鼓
I can begin to put myself together again.
多谢
你们
让我
大开
眼界。
还是不懂那是什么意思
Still don't know what that means.
等一下  你不是作者  但你和他一起工作过
So, wait, you weren't the author, but you worked with him.
那你记得他是谁吗
Do you remember who he was?
我正在努力回想
It's beginning to come back,
但我需要更多时间
but I need more time.
还有老花镜
And reading glasses. Heck!
我有好多记忆要回想
I got some rememberin' to do.
那  梅宝  你还想消除那些
So, Mabel, you still wanna erase
失败的夏日恋情的记忆吗
those failed summer romances?
谁都不喜欢糟糕的回忆
You know, no one likes having bad memories,
但我们或许更应该记住前车之鉴并从中吸取教训
but maybe it's better to remember the bad things
而不是拒绝接受  疯狂地想要遗忘
and learn from them than to go all denial crazy trying to forget.
梅宝  你开始成熟地胡说八道了哟
That's some mature junk right there, Mabel.
没错  成熟小姐就是我
Yep. Miss mature. That's me.
你们想不想帮我在混蛋前任暗恋对象的
Hey, you wanna help me vandalize this picture
照片上搞点小破坏啊
of my jerky ex-crush?
好哇
Ooh, yeah!
等等  给他画上龅牙
Wait, let's give him buck teeth.
我亲吻布偶
傻瓜
你猜怎么着
Hey, you know what?
参加这次大冒险着实让我
Going on this big adventure actually made me get
把那首蠢歌抛到脑后了  棒
that stupid song out of my head. Nice.
我是帅壕  姑娘  我们帅壕
<i>Am I blanchin', girl, we blanchin'</i>
拜托
Oh, come on!
看起来实在太熟悉了
It's all so familiar.
我几乎马上就要想起来了
It's almost like I can remember.
好的  已经越来越接近了
All right, you're getting closer.
反应每天都在变得更强
Every day, it's getting stronger.
哈  好啊
Ha! Yes! Ah!
我不在乎危不危险
I don't care if it's dangerous.
我不在乎要花多长时间
I don't care how long it takes.
我一定要成功
I'm gonna pull this off,
谁也别想阻止我
and no one's gonna get in my way.